-Hi.  - Hi.
-嗨.  - 嗨.
Do you have a table for three?
你们有一张桌子  给3个人吗?
Yes.
有的.
This way please.
这边请
We have a table over there, by the window. Or over here, by the wall.
我们有一张桌子在那边, 在窗户旁边 或者在这边, 在墙边.
That one?
那一个?
Yeah.
好的
What do you want?
你想要什么?
I want the eggplant.
我想要茄子.
Mmm.  How about you, Kevin?
Mmm. 你呢,Kevin?
I want the hamburger special.
我想要特色汉堡包.
No offense, Dean.
无意冒犯, Dean
I'm the vegetarian, not you.
我是素食主义者, 不是你.
What can I get for you?
我可以为你们弄点什么(吃的)?
The eggplant, please.
茄子, 请.
-I'm sorry. We don't have the eggplant. -Oh.
-对不起. 我们没有茄子. -Oh.
We have a nice baked vegetable parmesan.
我们有一个不错的烘好的蔬菜沙拉(vegetable parmesan).
That's fine.
那很好
-Do you have fruit salad? -Yes.
-你们有水果沙拉吗?  -有.
That please, with some rolls.
就要那个 请. 带有一些面包(rolls)
I want the hamburger special, please.
我想要特色汉堡包,请
With onions and peppers, and some vinegar for the fries.
包括洋葱和和胡椒粉, 和一些醋  为了薯条
Vinegar?
醋?
You can try one.
你可以试一个.
Do you want any drinks?
你们想要任何饮料吗?
Do you have that nice Italian mineral water?
你们有那个不错的意大利矿泉水吗?
Sure. Anything else?
有的. 还要别的吗?
No, thanks.
不,谢谢.
All set.
准备就绪.